<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Yichiban's Go</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io</link><description>ユリイカ</description><copyright>Yichiban's Go</copyright><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/160466378?v=4</url><title>avatar</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:28:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><managingEditor>Yichiban's Go</managingEditor><ttl>60</ttl><webMaster>Yichiban's Go</webMaster><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 8，Session2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%208%EF%BC%8CSession2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%208%EF%BC%8CSession2.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 8, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%208%2C%20Session%201.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%208%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Task - Week 7, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Task%20-%20Week%207%2C%20Session%202.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Task%20-%20Week%207%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 7, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%207%2C%20Session%201.html</link><description>Assignment 3 feels a bit difficult since this is the first time to do something in a 3D environment.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/a491469f-b087-4f89-9d81-abea81bef1dd)

This is the class activity first try, hope I can do better in the future

__About personal transformation

I think this is the hardest part because it is always hard for me to choose The transformation and the environment, how to blend them together to make a good concept is definitely the most difficult thing to express in the third stage.

Think of three transformations in class: big, medium and small

I think the biggest one is the two years I spent in Italy. I basically spent 17 to 18 years there. Those two years were the most exciting years of my life. I first lived in a small Italian town with a population of only 20,000 people for a year.

Small transformation I think it was the movie Chungking Express. Since then, I have become interested in the filming techniques and stories of movies.

I haven't figured out the medium transformation yet.

I hope the material can give a certain sense of reality and let people feel the texture.

I hope to use the sounds that we are familiar with in our daily lives, such as the sound of wind and grass, to give people a sense of harmony.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%207%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week6, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week6%2C%20Session%202.html</link><description>Review the homework tasks and blog entries that you have produced so far.

Speaking of the final adjustments, I didn’t actually finish in the last blog post. Mainly because I haven’t reached the final stage yet, so I’ll write a little more now.

In the final stage I make sure the icons can be displayed on the website and do a consistency check on the entire icon set to ensure that all icons are consistent in style, color, line thickness, etc.

_ Design Decisions_

• Functionality first: Consider the functionality of the icon first and ensure that each icon can intuitively express its corresponding function.

• Visual harmony: Use a consistent style and color scheme to ensure that the icon set blends seamlessly with the rest of the system or app.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/d5726472-0089-4c61-87ec-8d793c236fe3)
（still Google hahaha But I think this can be used as an example of icon style unification）

• User experience: Pay attention to the readability of icons on different devices and backgrounds to ensure that users can quickly recognize and use these icons regardless of the usage scenario.

Summarize:

I wanted to make specific design decisions every step of the way to ensure the icon set had the best balance between functionality, visuals, and user experience.

（I wanted to add some sense of space and distance to the flat design icon, so I used gradients and transparency to make it look less😆boring and like other icons. In the final stage, I reduced the shadow so I hope🙏it is still within the scope of flat design.）

Thank you for reading my blog, Professor🙏🙏🙏。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week6%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 13:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 6, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%206%2C%20Session%201.html</link><description>Remember to document your process and design decisions on your blog as you go,

About the design process and design decisions

My first step is to analyze the needs Thinking about what basic and additional features the user groups and audiences need and how to present them is like🤔thinking about the visual preferences of most people.

After that, it was concept development. Based on the needs analysis, after thinking about the overall style of the icons, I decided to adopt a simple and modern design to ensure that the icons are clearly identifiable under different backgrounds and conform to the overall aesthetic of the system application theme. There is also a basic color scheme. I decided to use gradient colors and soft color schemes to create a sense of depth visually while avoiding too strong color contrast to ensure that the entire set of icons can be harmoniously integrated into the interface.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/b3ebf9ef-f329-43d0-9c81-14e7740698e3)
（Just like this feeling, I also searched a lot on the Internet）

After that comes the preliminary design, which I sketch in my notebook to make sure the icons are visually consistent and convey their respective functions.

Then the detailed design is to further refine the details of the icon. The gradient shadow and semi-transparent effect are used to make the icon still have a three-dimensional feeling in the case of flat style, and it can also be differentiated from other similar social networking icons.

Finally, there is the final confirmation test and optimization. At that time, I will review my own icon and think about what to do for the icon at this time. Should I adjust the thickness of the line or reduce useless details? I will try to adjust it when the time comes.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%206%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 5, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%205%2C%20Session%202.html</link><description>Revisit the platform, context, and audience that you initially identified for your icons ?

For the platform of the icon, my keyword is system. Then I give it the context of social networking app. After all, most people use this kind of software on mobile phones. So for the platform, I chose mobile phones, including iOS and Android.


The design background of the icon. I hope it is modern and simple. In the early days of mobile phones, icons usually appeared in a realistic way. So I think it is a good idea to use simple lines to depict the shape of objects and add some lively colors.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/d90f7870-7357-431a-8423-62af97ba0d05)

I hope that the audience of icons should be very broad, including teenagers to middle-aged users. In order to attract and adapt to such a wide user group, icons need to have a certain degree of universality and ease of use. Therefore, moderate skeuomorphism is also necessary for icons. Users need to accurately and quickly understand the meaning of each icon.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/06d309c7-7549-41b2-b16d-3ae394fcbc50)

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/4a6008fe-77f0-47cc-a1eb-431bb227d5ca)

Experiment with swapping out the existing images in the template with your own prototype icon designs

sorry😢about this professor , I still don't understand a lot of things so the result is pretty bad。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%205%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 12:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 5, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%205%2C%20Session%201.html</link><description>4 Icons with 16 total colour variations.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/29587fc3-82cc-4718-b2d4-c572c0b75e60)

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/297d0137-c6c0-4434-b7f9-0c0bb4a8b263)

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/3caf7394-9943-4f4a-aa25-a3e8e14c76aa)

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/a53f4a9d-076c-428b-9967-8bbfa3631722)

I prefer the color scheme of Monochromatic because the keyword of the theme I want to design is system.

My goal was to design a set of icons that were consistent, simple, and focused on functionality, so the Monochromatic color scheme was a great choice. It maintains the overall harmony of the design while helping users focus on the meaning and functionality of the icons.

Finally, I think the mono chromatic color scheme is very easy to maintain consistency and it also makes it easier for me to do subsequent icon design.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%205%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week4, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week4%2C%20Session%202.html</link><description>Thumbnail Sketching Activity&#13;
This is the yerba mate🧉cup I drew&#13;
&#13;
I like the second bird's-eye view. You can see the tea straws in the cup like pillars falling from the sky. It's very simple and the effect looks ok.&#13;
&#13;
 ![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/a6f5d8bf-ac08-4edf-a588-0d71e9e636a1)&#13;
&#13;
Sketch of the icon created for assignment 2&#13;
&#13;
'Icons are a powerful form communication that can cross cultural and language barriers'(From slideshows)

I remember Elon Musk said at a blog summit two years ago that he hoped to use WeChat as a template to transform Twitter.(I don't know if this is true or false🤔)

To make a long story short, he felt that there was no such a unified application as WeChat in my hometown. You can post comments on WeChat, publish videos, and earn revenue from content creation.（WeChat is more like WhatsApp plus PayPal plus Instagram plus Twitter As of the end of the third quarter of 2023, WeChat's monthly active users reached 1.336 billion）

For the whole set of icons, I hope to give people a friendly feeling, so I will avoid making icons with edges and corners. Icons with arcs or round shapes will be better.

At the same time, texture is also what I want to emphasize. After all, it is a great thing🤩to be able to express the texture of an icon through the screen.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/d3101445-ed8d-4a04-8fb9-c8eb3035124c)

Regarding file backup, many companies also like to use the cloud. Maybe they want users to think that their backups are in the cloud☁️, so they are safer. So I hope to clearly describe the feeling of uploading and downloading. In the end, I may choose the one with the upload symbol☝️.

Regarding searching, I have looked for some inspirations online or simply looked at the designs of some companies, but most of them are magnifying glasses🔍, which is a bit boring. And I can't think of a particularly good alternative🕵️‍♂️. So I might replace it in the end. Maybe it would be nice to make a folder icon to go with the file back up.

If possible, I would like to use horizontal lines for the contact icon because it gives people a sense of stability. The contact icon should contain our relatives and friends, so if possible, avoiding overly square lines is also an option. It is also good to have some arcs or give some round feeling. I may choose the first icon.

The collection icon contains things we like or find useful, so it can be interpreted as a desire for knowledge. Vertical lines can be a kind of usage element. Its characteristic is demanding of attention. After all, we will definitely look for the content again after we collect🌟it. I might do the first one.

Regarding information icons, the first thing that comes to my mind is diagonal lines because it is energetic, implying impending change. We always have expectations and uneasiness about unknown news, so diagonal is a good choice. I might make it the fifth one.

Regarding the album icon, there are many styles when I was looking for it, such as a colorful windmill with a certain degree of transparency and a simple landscape outlined by lines. I want to use straight lines and some curves to depict the mountains. There is a small🗻hill behind the mountain with a sense of🌆sunset, and maybe a small sun on it.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/6c814eb0-4a8c-465c-bca2-d2513944c405)

The discover icon is essentially to check the latest updates from friends, so there are many things that can represent the🧭compass and the mysterious📦box. However, I want to use a curve to draw the planet icon because it gives people a feeling of exploring in space, and it would be best if it has a ring like Saturn🪐, so I should choose the fourth one.

Regarding wallets, I think the most commonly used👝wallet is the best representation. A slight curve can bring a sense of calm to the wallet icon. After all, everyone hopes that the money in their wallet is💳safe. I might choose the fifth one.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week4%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:06:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks-Week 4, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks-Week%204%2C%20Session%201.html</link><description>Black Square Activity 

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/262636f3-cd22-42d2-852a-6bf0092b715b)

As a student who is new to illustrator, I think I will use shape tools, pen tool, path editing, alignment and distribution, color and gradient, transparency and blending modes in my work.

Design Thinking

Empathize
• Gather data and collect  data :gather user expectations and feedback on icons through interviews, questionnaires, or observations.
👍
Define 
• Problem definition: Based on the information collected, identify the core problem that needs to be solved when designing the icon.
👍
Ideate
• Mind Mapping: Use mind maps to organize and expand ideas and explore different design directions.
👍
Prototype
• Rapid prototyping: Create preliminary sketches or digital prototypes of your icon design.
👍
Test
• Functionality testing: Ensure the functionality and usability of icons on different devices and platforms.
👍
Implement
• Final design: Complete the final icon design based on the test results.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/01400989-883b-4184-bace-372f7ede5b93)

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/5a1a4022-fd4f-4fac-b153-8603e855e0c8)


I originally had three ideas. The PlayStation system icon has simple lines that can tell the user what the icon is used for. I also thought of an icon for the weather app, but there are only a few types of weather, such as sunny, rainy, snowy, cloudy, etc. The other one is a game icon. I actually like this idea very much. I even drew a rough sketch. But recently I tried it and found that it is too difficult for me to challenge the game icon at my current level.

So recently I thought of social networking apps. Actually I think this is not bad. We use it almost every day. Think about the billions of people who use social networking apps in the world. What a huge user group. As for why I chose this theme, system, I think we use these apps every day, but when we are used to using it, we will forget about these icons and just rely on our subconscious to react to them. So I think you must be an excellent designer👨‍🎨to be able to make this feeling. Different functions in the app can become icons, so I want to design icons for it. The specific platform is the mobile phone. The background is some basic functions. The audience on the social networking app I hope is everyone, regardless of gender, age or young, but I hope the icon design is a little more interesting, so it may also be more inclined to a slightly younger group.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks-Week%204%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Supplement to scavenger hunt</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Supplement%20to%20scavenger%20hunt.html</link><description>I wrote in my scavenger hunt blog that our group didn't find much so I later went looking for some more items like those on the list.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/a24abf29-d262-4bc0-a922-e2d6d968d55b)

probably An explosive cup of coffee.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/7e97abfc-0587-4c20-9bee-6c408db7addc)

Wooden things like statues or cloaks probably A curtain of roots
, delivered by a winged visitor.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/7e44c9fe-ad09-4fd9-ab29-00df05829936)

A book containing Digital Media wisdom, found amongst many.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/e2aeaa44-1e4b-4afc-b7ee-2dda33027433)

A study space fit for a Sith Lord 

(About selfies🤳My group and I tried it before but the photos were ugly so we gave up. Sorry about that.)。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Supplement%20to%20scavenger%20hunt.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 12:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 3, Session1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%203%2C%20Session1.html</link><description>https://youtu.be/4TGwaPqWTDU?si=32F9rQJ3qKRgZEer

The process of making a draft

I thought of many ideas, such as using the changes in the shadow 👥 under the light to introduce myself, treating the doll 🧸 as myself and only shooting the doll, and only shooting the back of my head in the video, but to be honest, these are a bit difficult for me to shoot alone because I am alone.

Finally, I chose to shoot my hands and feet to express the changes and movements of the hands in different scenes. This is actually more difficult than I thought. How to express the natural movements of the hands and how to express the changes of light and shadow on the hands?

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/b6fd8b10-b95c-4e94-ad32-05e095ffb566)

Of course, it is best to present it naturally, but I have to put the phone in a stable position to shoot. I actually have a lot of things I want to present, but it is difficult for me to do it at this stage. Just like the directors in the movies, they can shoot the hands like ballet dancers, so the movement of the hands is a problem for me.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/ff0f7e2c-b0a0-4094-b519-cfa59349af39)

The topic of hands is also very interesting to me because I remember that AI-made paintings and videos often make mistakes on hands. Michelangelo's oil painting Creation of Eve, Adam's outstretched fingers represent what it means to me is a beginning and a connection, so I hope that my hands in the video can also have a meaning, just like a fist 👊 can represent courage and anger, the hands I present in the video are more like representing myself, my emotions, and my feelings.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/ef77b095-c11e-46da-9b2f-4cdced69020c)

And this is Dürer's Praying Hands 🙏 A very important painting in art history. When I was writing this article ✍️, I suddenly thought of this painting. I guess this painting can better represent my thoughts.

（Professor, if you can see this, I would really appreciate it🙏 I wrote too much and my writing is not good. Only text looks too boring, so I added some emojis. Thank You Again for your patience.）。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%203%2C%20Session1.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 11:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 2, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%202%2C%20Session%202.html</link><description>Question: Key moments in the two-minute video ?

Answer: As the creator of this video, I like the beginning and the end of this video. If I have to choose, I would choose the end because if possible, I hope that the viewers will think that this is an interesting idea when they see the end.

Question: How I planing to use Sound design and soundtrack to construct this moment ?

Answer: At the end I took videos of the lake, the temple, the flowing water and finally I wrote down my expectations for the future.

So these are all calm shots. I used ambient sounds and slow guitars to create a balance between the audio and visual elements. The sound of water, wind, and the sound of a book closing are all elements.

Question: Emotional tone How editing will support that tone?

Answer: The coherent editing and emotional tone are what I want to present. I hope that people who watch my video will at least feel relaxed when watching my video, so I don’t want the ending to be illogical, so I hope that there won’t be any particularly fast-cut editing at the end.

Question: The relationship between the shots I want to establish?

Answer: For me, the relationship between shots is important. If the continuity of the shots is disrupted, the video will feel weird. So I hope that each shot or the next shot is logical and does not make people feel out of place.

Question: Trying to establish the rhythm beat speed editing how to produce this effect?

Answer: At the end, I hope to make a fade-out with the I close the book, and there is also the sound of running water. I want to make a G cut. I hope the ambient sound can give people a feeling of comfort and texture.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/7a76838e-8039-46b4-b9ff-f57285bb04c4)

The first shot of the hand lying on the bench by the sea with ambient sound and background music.

The second shot is the sound of returning home and throwing keys on the table.

The third shot is the sound of brewing yerba mate tea and background music.

The fourth shot Go game ambient sound and fade-in.

The fifth shot is the sound of cooking and background music.

The sixth one I put my hands together 🙏 There is no ambient sound because it is too noisy outside, so there is only background music.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%202%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks -Week 2, Session 1</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-Week%202%2C%20Session%201.html</link><description>![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/201a6e0e-e47f-4325-9513-2097feb6c519)

The first shot is from the shoes in the crowd, switching to my shoes, In my opinion, this is a kind of continuity. For example, the pen in my hand when the pen fall the light turns green.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/b7919596-aa6e-4d4a-90ba-448f4bfaa5b4)

When the green light comes out, I write something in my notebook and then connect with some conceptual stuff.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/5b6cd667-aa65-4242-8763-85a2074fd722)

The third picture I wanted to express a sense of discontinuity, similar to a jump cut, but the final result might not be very good. The content is mainly about me going out.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/69270626-cb47-46ea-a08a-5a75d58f7fa9)

The fourth photo shows my hobbies: playing chess, cooking, and drinking mate. I also occasionally go out for a walk. I hope to show a calm emotion, so the movements are usually fixed or the movements are relatively small.

Question:The editing method influences the main themes, concepts, actions and feelings I want to present to the viewer ?

Answer: I want to give people a sense of calmness, so the movements are not big during the shooting. But in the middle part, I want to show the dynamics, so I want to create a sense of discontinuity. At other times, I basically hope that the video editing is logical, that is, to maintain coherence. There are also some conceptual things, such as green plants and sunshine. I hope there is a meaning in them, perhaps growth or simply to tell the viewer that it is dawn.

(Sorry, professor, if you see this, I need to say sorry because my storyboard is really bad I'm not used to drawing on the computer.)。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-Week%202%2C%20Session%201.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 09:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Homework Tasks - Week 1, Session 2</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%201%2C%20Session%202.html</link><description>https://youtu.be/7ynDcNB4T9g?si=CB2Z5z2P4Ad-q1JM

How successful I feel 

I think the success rate is about 30%. I took the video of the scenery on the tram. I used to live in the suburbs, so I was far away from the school. So I didn't know what to take a video of, so I took a video of the scenery outside the tram windows.

Doria took a video of the state library and Julie took a video of her desk at home.

Some brief reflections on that process

I think the videos I shoot are boring, only the scenery. Maybe I need something more interesting. This requires me to learn editing skills like other video bloggers.

Aiming for

I hope that one day I can learn more practical skills so that one day I can watch more of my own videos at least I won’t be bored. But I’m lazy so I hope I can do it one day.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/Homework%20Tasks%20-%20Week%201%2C%20Session%202.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 04:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SCAVERGER HUNT 25/JULY</title><link>https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/SCAVERGER%20HUNT%2025-JULY.html</link><description>On Monday, Julie, Fiona and I went scavenger hunting in the school with clues and maps. It was not easy becasue there were many things I couldn’t understand, and things I could’t find.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/a55348f3-d0bc-4a4c-8c34-1b611a7b8328)

GOLDEN GLOBE ATOP A TOWER OF EIGHTS.

julie found it not me,well i guess she’s much better than me unless at this part.

![image](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/030e303f-93f3-4138-a1ec-34c358c6e1c8)

HE DISEMBODIED HANDS OF A GREAT APE.

It was easy to found, Cause I with their team so I found it but why is there a gorilla’s hand in the school ?。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://yichiban1.github.io/yichiban.github.io/post/SCAVERGER%20HUNT%2025-JULY.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>